Kelber, Harry Audio-Visual Materials 6371 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Harry Kelber Audio-Visual Materials
1975-2006
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Kelber, Harry
6371 AV
2.11 cubic feet
2.1 linear ft.
Audio-visual materials.
8399857
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, February 21, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, March 07, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Kelber, Harry
8399857
- An Evening with Harry Kelber (May 16, 2006), 1 (Box 1)
- Organizing (1975), 1 (Box 2)
- Dr. Harry Kelber Endowment in Labor Studies - May 9, 1984, Sheraton Centre, 2 (Box 2)
- Harry @ Local 3 - 1985, 3 (Box 2)
- Restoring Employee Rights is Good for America: The Campaign for Employee Rights - A Joint Project of 1199, 4 (Box 2)
- War Zone March & Rally - 6/25/1995, 5 (Box 2)
  Scope and Contents
  un-edited
- Leadership Training (PILOT) #1 -- May 6-7, 1987 - Dr. Harry Kelber, 6 (Box 2)
- Harry Kelber in Florida, 7 (Box 2)
- The Democratic Promise, 8 (Box 2)
- Organizing: The Right to Dignity, 9 (Box 2)
- Labor on the Job: Banned from the Paris-Workers Challenge AFL-CIO Leadership, 10 (Box 2)
- Our Class of People, 11 (Box 2)
- Brother Harry Arsdale, 12 (Box 2)
- Critical Thinking - Oct. 21, 1987, 13 (Box 2)
- The Faces of a Union, 14 (Box 2)
- The State of the Union, 15 (Box 2)
- The Grievance, 16 (Box 2)
- Arbitration: The Seven Tests of Just Cause, 17 (Box 2)
- Struggle in the Heartland, 18 (Box 2)
- We Can Do It at PTP!, 19 (Box 2)
- America's Victory: The 1997 UPS Strike, 20 (Box 2)
- Brother Harry Van Arsdale (tape 2), 21 (Box 2)
- Leadership Training (PILOT) #2 -- May 6-7, 1987 - Dr. Harry Kelber, 22 (Box 2)
- Point of Order: Part 1 - The Dynamics of Parliamentary Order; Part 2 Parliamentary Order and Group Interaction, 1 (Box 3)
- Trip to BAL Harbour, Fl - 2/17-22/1995 - tape 1 (unedited), 2 (Box 3)
  Candid discussions: Meeting with Sec. of Labor R. Riech; Ken Coss - URW Int. Pres.
- Trip to Bal Harbour, Fl - 2/17-22/1995 - tape 2 (unedited), 3 (Box 3)
  More discussions - Harry Kelber; Photo Op of Ex. Board - discussion of trip
- A New Voice For American Workers - Rally - 7/31/1995 -- URW-USA Demo at Japanese Embassy & Firestone Headquarters - Chicago, IL - 7/31/1995 (unedited), 4 (Box 3)
- Harry Kelber - Labor Notes - 9/13/2003 - Detroit, 5 (Box 3)
- ACTWU-ILGWU Merger Press Conf. -- 220/1995; Lane Kirkland Press Conf. - 2/20/1995; Lane Kirkland Press Cong. - 2/22/1995, 6 (Box 3)
- Five Days That Shook the Teamsters, 7 (Box 3)
- The Teamsters: Whose Union is it?, 8 (Box 3)
- Struggling Unions, 9 (Box 3)
- Think Tank - 2/21/1981, 10 (Box 3)
- Restoring Employee Rights is good for America, 11 (Box 3)
- AIW Local 837 - Deadly Corn, 12 (Box 3)
- Fifty Years of Industrial Unionism - Industrial Union Dept. AFL-CIO, 13 (Box 3)
- Locked Out!, 14 (Box 3)
- Demensions of Bargaining, 15 (Box 3)